hide-my-ip.com 2019-12-09

# Our Privacy Policy

Your privacy is a top priority to us. This document discloses our data collection and usage policies.

In this policy, "we", "us", and "our" means My Privacy Tools, Inc. This policy briefly describes the personally identifiable information that we may collect from our users or customers and the process of safeguarding this information. By using any of our products, services, network, or visiting our websites, you agree we may use your personal information as outlined below. By using or accessing the My Privacy Tools, Inc websites, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. 

#### Collection of Your Personal Information

We may collect your personal information when you:  

  * Purchase or obtain a product or service from us.
  * Make contact with us for any reason.
  * Use or access any of our our products, services, websites, or network.

We may also collect information about you from other organizations, if this is appropriate such as but not limited to fraud prevention agencies or business directories. 

#### Cookies

We may use "cookies", small data files saved in your web browser, to improve the quality of our website, improve user and customer interaction with us during purchasing, setup, billing, support matters. You may block the use of such "cookies" in your web browser settings or by using third-party cookie blocking utilities, however doing so may limit the availability of certain features of our website.  

#### Collected Personal Information

We do not monitor or keep logs your Internet traffic or activity while using the service. The information we collect about you depends on the products and services you use or purchase from My Privacy Tools, Inc. Such information may include, but not limited to:  

  * Your name, address, E-mail address, IP address, and other information required to validate your identity when you make contact with us regarding your account or payment.
  * Credit or debit card information or other payment information.
  * Use or access any of our our products, services, websites, or network.
  * Any communication with us, such as a ticket request to our support team, an E-mail, or live chat session. 
  * Your account information, such as billing dates, subscription type, and account details. 
  * Information relating to your use of our websites.
  * Browser visit time and access duration to our website.

#### Using Your Personal Information

Your privacy is safe with our no-logging policy for all VPN and proxy products. Information you provide to us through our website, CRM software, or applications is used to maintain quality service and:  

  * Provide you the products and services you have purchased or from us. 
  * Update you about new products and services, unless you have opted out of our marketing communications. 
  * Contact you with offers based on how you use our products and services. 
  * Reply to any inquiries you may have about our products, services, website, or network. 
  * Prevent fraud or other crimes, or recover debts.

We will retain your personal information for as long as your account or product is active or as needed to provide you services. In the event you terminate your relationship with My Privacy Tools, Inc, we may retain personal information necessary to resolve disputes, enforce our user agreement, protect our legal rights, or comply with legal and technical requirements related to the security, function, and operation of My Privacy Tools, inc products, services, network and websites. Otherwise, we will only store your personal information for as long as necessary to provide you services, comply with the law, and to run our business. My Privacy Tools, Inc or one of our partners or agents may contact you about My Privacy Tools, Inc related services during this time if you have not already chosen to opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us. 

#### Sharing Your Personal Information

My Privacy Tools, Inc will never sell, trade, give, transfer, or disclose personally identifiable information to third parties for unrelated marketing purposes. We may share information about you with:  

  * Companies owned by My Privacy Tools, Inc.
  * Agents or partners who we have chosen to support the products and services you purchase or use. 
  * Companies that provide services for us, including fraud prevention services. 
  * Debt collection agencies or other debt recovery organizations.
  * Law enforcement, regulatory, or other public authorities if required to do so by law. 

We may share information to protect us from fraud, protect our rights and property, or to protect the rights of our users and customers. In case My Privacy Tools, Inc is sold to another organization or reorganized, we may transfer any of your personal information to the new or acquiring organization. 

#### System Security

My Privacy Tools, Inc employs a variety of network security tools that monitor our network for problems and prevent hacking, abuse, fraud, data loss, and other misuses of our web site or data. We operational guidelines in place to safeguard user and customer privacy, and will continue to update and enhance new security features as applicable.  

#### Children's Online Privacy Protection Act

The privacy and protection of children is especially important to us. My Privacy Tools, Inc does not sell products or services for purchase by children. As per the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, we do not collect personally identifiable information from children without prior parental consent nor do we provide links to external web sites that are inappropriate for children. My Privacy Tools, Inc does not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from minors under the age of eighteen. In addition, My Privacy Tools, Inc will not knowingly link to any third party web site that solicits or collects customer identifiable information from minors. If you believe that a minor has disclosed personally identifiable information to My Privacy Tools, Inc, please contact us at so that the information can be removed. 

#### Automated Decision Making Policy

My Privacy Tools, Inc does not engage in automated decision-making.  

#### Personal Information Non-Disclosure

Our employees or staff are prohibited during and after their employment or contract period with My Privacy Tools, Inc from disclosing personal information to any person or entity outside of our company except for the reasons already described above. Our employees or staff are only allowed to disclose the personal information of a user or customer to other employees or staff who require access to the information to provide service to the user or customer.  

#### Spam Policy

Use of any product, service, website, or network of My Privacy Tools, Inc for spamming purposes is not allowed. Using our products, service, website, or network for spam can result in suspension of access privileges. 

#### Location of Your Personal Information

My Privacy Tools, Inc websites and data are located in the United States. By using or accessing our websites or providing us with any personal information, you consent to the transfer, processing and storage of your personal information in the United States. For residents of the EEA, some or all of your personal information may be stored or transferred out of the EEA, for any reason, including for example, if our product database, CRM, or third-party analytics systems is located in a country outside the EEA or if any of our service providers or their servers or data centers are located outside of the EEA. We will only transfer or keep your personal information with organizations that have provided adequate safeguards in respect of your personal data and are compliant of EEA privacy and data protection laws.  

#### Data Protection Policy and Your Rights

Residents of the EEA have the following protection rights for their personal information:  

  * By logging into your account or contacting our support, you may access, correct or update any of your personal information that you provided to us. 
  * You may opt-out of any marketing communications we send you at any time by contacting our support or by clicking any "unsubscribe" link in the marketing emails we send to you. 
  * You may request deletion of any of your personal information at any time by contacting us using the contact information below. It may take up to a 30 days to complete any request. 
  * Additionally, if you have questions, inquiries, or requests regarding the processing of your personal information you may contact us at: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), or you may write to us at: 

My Privacy Tools, Inc.   
7770 Regents Rd. Suite #113-644  
San Diego, CA 92122-1967   
United States
